Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
16-2-2156
Cornell University. College of Engineering.
105.1 cubic ft.
Correspondence, published reports, minutes of meetings
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dean's Office subject files, including correspondence, annual reports, minutes of meetings, and working papers concerning the establishment of programs and construction of buildings. Includes the administrative papers of Deans Andrew Schultz, William Streett, T. E. Everhart, Edmund Cranch, and Solomon Hollister. Earlier records consist primarily of the records of Assistant Engineering Dean John F. McManus. Also, blank Fuertes Medal for graduate research in civil engineering.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Dean's Office subject files, including correspondence, annual reports, minutes of meetings, and working papers concerning the establishment of programs and construction of buildings. Includes the administrative papers of Deans Andrew Schultz, William Streett, T. E. Everhart, Edmund Cranch, and Solomon Hollister. Earlier records consist primarily of the records of Assistant Engineering Dean John F. McManus. Also, blank Fuertes Medal for graduate research in civil engineering.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cranch, Edmund T.(Edmund Titus), 1922-; Everhart, Thomas E.; Hollister, Solomon Cady, b. 1891.; McManus, John F.; Schultz, Andrew Schultz, 1913-; Streett, William B.(William Bernard), 1932-
Subjects:
Engineering--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to the permission of the office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Commencement arrangements, 1968-1971 (Box 1)
- Inauguration,Presidents Perkins, Corson & Rhodes (Box 1)
- Centennial celebration (Box 1)
- Commencement arrangements, 1941-1967 (Box 2)
- Minutes: Civil Engineering, September 22, 1921-June 13, 1934 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Civil Engineering, September 28, 1936-October 4, 1937 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Civil Engineering, April 10, 1939-March 25, 1946 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Civil Engineering, ca. 1945 -1950 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Electrical Engineering, March 29, 1921-July 30, 1934 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Electrical Engineering, August 14, 1936-March 14, 1938 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Electrical Engineering, ca. 1940-1950 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Mechanical Engineering, October 17, 1921-June 18, 1934 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Mechanical Engineering, October 19, 1936-March 7, 1938 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Mechanical Engineering, 1941 -1950 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Engineering Division, Graduate School, March 14, 1933- February 19, 1938 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Engineering College, February 21, 1921-June 20, 1924 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Engineering College, October 28, 1929-March 20, 1935 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Engineering College, February 1940-May 1943 (Box 3)
- Minutes: Engineering College, August 16, 1943-June 27, 1946 (Box 3)
- Student Ratings, Jr. and Senior - Electrical Engineers, 1929-February 1947 (Box 4)
- Student Ratings, Jr. and Senior - Mechanical Engineers, 1929-1940 (Box 4)
- Student Ratings, Jr. and Senior - Civil Engineers, 1937-1947 (Box 5)
- Student Ratings, Jr. and Senior - Chemical. Engineers, 1933-1948 (Box 5)
- Student Ratings, Jr. and Senior - Mechanical Engineers, 1942-1948 (Box 5)
- Student Ratings, Jr. and Senior - Administrative Engineers, 1934-1944 (Box 5)
- Alumni Survey, Coll. of Engineering, 1916 (Box 6)
- Faculty & Alumni publicity material, 1937-1943 (Box 7)
- Engineering College Development Record (Box 8)
- Historical correspondence & reports misc., ca. 1885-1940 (Box 9)
- Hollister - "Report on the College of Engineering at Cornell University, 1950 (Box 9)
- Buildings data, 1953 (Box 9)
- Building plant proposals, 1925, 1936, 1939, 1950's (Box 9)
- McManus articles (Box 9)
- Secondary school career days, ca. 1950-1955 (Box 9)
- Mechanical Engineering inventory, 1938-1940 (Box 10)
- College of Engineering inventory, 1950-1951 (Box 10)
- Short courses (e.g. "extension"), 1930's, 1940's (Box 10)
- Student scholarships, rules, activities, 1940's-1950's (Box 10)
- Student petitions and decisions, 1885-1900 (Box 10)
- E.S.MWT-E.S.MDT (Box 11-)
- World War II Training Programs (Box 12)
- Graduate evening courses - Industrial evening courses, 1961-1963 (Box 13)
- Engineers Council for Professional Development, 1950-1951 (Box 13)
- Center for Environmental Quality Management, 1966-1973 (Box 13)
- Assoc. of Engineering Colleges of New York State, 1974-1977 (Box 13)
- American Society for Engineering Education, Regional, 1966, 1977 (Box 14)
- Alumni Trustee Elections, 1952-1958 (Box 14)
- Publicity releases, ca. 1940-1946 (Box 14)
- College of Engineering, unit budgets, 1950-1951 (Box 14)
- COSEP, 1969-1977 (Box 15)
- Selective Service, 1968-1971 (Box 15)
- 2x2 slides, Coll. of Engineering, 1950's, 1960's (Box 15)
- Misc. records re planning, courses, attrition, enrollment, 1965-1971 (Box 16)
- Misc. records, 1942-1966 (Box 17)
- American Association of Engineering Societies, Inc. (AAES), 1983 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- American Society for Engineering Education (A.S.E.E.) Engineering College Council (EEC) Executive Board, 1976-1984 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- A.S.E.E.- General, 1979-1984 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Academic Counseling and Advising Services Special Committee to Study and Review, 1982-1982 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Committee on Academic Freedom and Responsibility, 1974-1983 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Academy for Educational Development - Award, 1982 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology (ABET), 1983-1984 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Admissions- Enrollment and Attrition, 1970-1980 (Box 18, Folder 8-11)
- Admissions, (R.E. Gardner) Special File that T.E, Everhart had in his office, 1979-1984 (Box 18, Folder 12-15)
- Computer Systems for Admissions & Registrar, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Admissions- Engineering, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 17-20)
- Admissions, Engineering, 1982-1984 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- Admissions, Engineering- General Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 18, Folder 22-23)
- Admissions- General Correspondence, 1973-1980 (Box 18, Folder 24-26)
- Admissions, Engineering- Applications for Director, Assistant Director, Assistant Director (Minorities), n.d. (Box 18, Folder 27)
- Admissions, 1966-1973 (Box 18, Folder 28-35)
- Admissions, Engineering- Minorities, 1976-1984 (Box 18, Folder 36-38)
- Dean's List, 1982-1986 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Engineer Deans' Institutes and Meetings, 1980-1987 (Box 19, Folder 2-5)
- D Correspondences, 1960-1971 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Deans- Big Ten Meetings, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 7-8)
- Dean's Council, 1960-1968 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Dean's Council, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Dean's Council, 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 11-14)
- Dean's Council, 1970-1971 (Box 19, Folder 15-16)
- Dean's Council, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Dean's Council, 1972-1973 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Dean's Council, 1973-1974 (Box 19, Folder 19-21)
- Dean's Council, 1974-1975 (Box 19, Folder 22-23)
- Dean's Council, 1975-1976 (Box 19, Folder 24-25)
- Dean's Council, 1976-1978 (Box 19, Folder 26-28)
- Dean's Council, 1978-1979 (Box 19, Folder 29-30)
- Dean's Council, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 31-33)
- Dean's Council, 1981-1982 (Box 19, Folder 34-35)
- Dean's Council, 1982-1983 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Dean's Council, 1983-1984 (Box 20, Folder 2-3)
- Dean's Council, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 4-5)
- Agency for International Development (A.I.D.), 1964-1972 (Box 20, Folder 6-8)
- A.I.D., 1972-1974 (Box 20, Folder 9-12)
- A.I.D., 1974-1983 (Box 20, Folder 13-16)
- Aluminum Company of America, 1958-1959 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Annual Reports, 1948-1964 (Box 20, Folder 18-20)
- Annual Reports, 1964-1967 (Box 20, Folder 21-22)
- Annual Reports, 1967-1970 (Box 20, Folder 23-24)
- Annual Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 20, Folder 25)
- Annual Reports, 1971-1972 (Box 20, Folder 26)
- Applied and Engineering Physics, 1973-1975 (Box 20, Folder 27-29)
- Applied and Engineering Physics, 1975-1980 (Box 20, Folder 30-34)
- Applied and Engineering Physics, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 1-6)
- Applied and Engineering Physics, 1982-1985 (Box 21, Folder 7-10)
- Aero Engineering, 1958-1972 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1956-1966 (Box 21, Folder 12-14)
- American Association Land Grant Colleges, 1959-1966 (Box 21, Folder 15-17)
- Applied Mathematics, 1963-1983 (Box 21, Folder 18-23)
- Applied Physics, 1965-1973 (Box 21, Folder 24-28)
- Army, U.S. (Misc.), 1959 (Box 21, Folder 29)
- ASARCO, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 30)
- American Society of Civil Engineers, 1957-1970 (Box 21, Folder 31)
- American Society for Engineering Education (A.S.E.E.) Research and Graduate Study Directory, 1983-1984 (Box 21, Folder 32)
- A.S.E.E. Research and Graduate Study Directory, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 33)
- A.S.E.E. Engineering and Graduate Study, 1973-1983 (Box 21, Folder 34-37)
- A.S.E.E. General, 1974-1979 (Box 21, Folder 38-39)
- A.S.E.E. Engineering Dean's Council Board Meeting in Hilton Head, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 40)
- American Society for Testing Materials (ASTM), 1959-1964 (Box 21, Folder 41)
- Association of Engineering College of New York State, 1979-1983 (Box 22, Folder 1-5)
- Association of Engineering College of New York State, 1983-1986 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Affirmative Action, 1979-1984 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Agriculture, College of, 1981-1987 (Box 22, Folder 8-10)
- American Association of Engineering Societies, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- American Cyanamid Co., 1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- American Electric Power Corp., 1970-1984 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- American Petroleum Partners, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Announcements- Distribution, 1973-1978 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Acola, 1968-1985 (Box 22, Folder 16-17)
- Applied Mathematics, 1983-1988 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Applied and Engineering, School of- 5 Year Plan, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 19-21)
- Armington, Charles R. Scholarship, 1973 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- AT&T, 1975-1986 (Box 22, Folder 23-24)
- Awards and Prizes, 1976-1984 (Box 22, Folder 25-26)
- B- General Correspondences, 1961-1971 (Box 22, Folder 27-29)
- Bard, F.N., 1947-1962 (Box 22, Folder 30-32)
- Bard, F.N., 1963-1988 (Box 22, Folder 33-34)
- Basic Studies, Division of, 1974-1977 (Box 22, Folder 35-37)
- Bausch & Lornb Edward B. Memorial Lab, 1961-1980 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Beebor. A.M., 1959-1977 (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
- Bell Telephone Lab (Master's Program), 1962-1975 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Bell Telephone Laboratories, 1963-1983 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Berth, Donald F., 1965-1984 (Box 23, Folder 5-9)
- Bioengineering, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 10-11)
- Biological Facility N.I.H. (Finn), 1966 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Biology Program, 1963-1972 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Biophysics, 1973-1977 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Biotechnology Proposal- Correspondence, 1982-1984 (Box 23, Folder 15-16)
- Biotechnology Proposal- Correspondence, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 17-20)
- Black Studies, 1969-1972 (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
- Boley, Bruno A., 1967-1972 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Building Program, 1957-1958 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Burr, A.H., 1966-1976 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Burton, Malcolm, 1980-1983 (Box 23, Folder 26-27)
- C, 1960-1962 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Capitol Projects, 1974-1978 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Civil Engineering (C.E.)- Faculty, 1957-1963 (Box 23, Folder 30-31)
- C.E. Hydraulics Laboratory, 1949-1961 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Centennial Celebration, 1960-1965 (Box 23, Folder 33-34)
- Centennial Trethaway, Edward J., 1963-1965 (Box 23, Folder 35)
- Civil Engineering Reorganization, 1962-1966 (Box 23, Folder 36)
- Chemical Engineering, 1947-1967 (Box 24, Folder 1-4)
- Chemical Engineering, 1964-1974 (Box 24, Folder 5-6)
- Chemical Engineering, 1974-1981 (Box 24, Folder 7-8)
- Chemical Engineering, 1981-1982 (Box 24, Folder 9-11)
- Chemical Engineering, 1982-1983 (Box 24, Folder 12-14)
- Chemical Engineering Study, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Cornell High Energy Synchrotron Source (C.H.E.S.S.), 1979-1984 (Box 24, Folder 16-19)
- Chicago Pneumatic Tool Co., 1983-1987 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- China, People's Republic of, 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 21-22)
- People's Republic of China- Microelectronics Seminar, 1978-1981 (Box 24, Folder 23-25)
- People's Republic of China- Microelectronics Seminar, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 26-27)
- China Trip (Cornell), 1979-1983 (Box 24, Folder 28-29)
- China Trip- National Science Foundation, 1980-1981 (Box 24, Folder 30)
- Cornell Industrial Innovation Service (C.I.I.S.), 1985 (Box 24, Folder 31)
- Civil Defense, 1963 (Box 24, Folder 32)
- Clark Hall Space, 1981 (Box 24, Folder 33)
- College of Engineering- Report on by C.S. Hollister, 1950 (Box 24, Folder 34)
- College of Engineering- Priority Studying and Financial Plan by E.T. Cranch, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 35-36)
- College Legislation, 1967-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1-2)
- Computer, 1959-1964 (Box 25, Folder 3-7)
- Cooperative Program- Engineering, 1979-1984 (Box 25, Folder 8-9)
- Coors, J. - Proposal, 1972-1989 (Box 25, Folder 10-11)
- Cornell in Perspective, 1967-1973 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Cornell Programs in New York City, 1967 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Course Registration Data, 1965-1973 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Cornell Reorganization, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 15-16)
- Cornell Research Foundation, 1959-1984 (Box 25, Folder 17-20)
- College Situation, 1970-1979 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Cornell Society of Engineers (C.S.E.), 1961-1963 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- CS.E., 1962-1967 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- C.S.E., 1965-1973 (Box 25, Folder 24-25)
- C.S.E., 1973-1982 (Box 25, Folder 26-29)
- C.S.E. Message to Alumni, 1970-1983 (Box 25, Folder 30-31)
- CS.E., 1983-1984 (Box 25, Folder 32-35)
- C.S.E. Distinguished Teaching Award, 1963-1983 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Cornell Special File Spring, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 37-38)
- Cornell University Associates, 1960-1961 (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Cornell University Centennial Program, 1957-1958 (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Cornell University Council, 1958-1966 (Box 26, Folder 1-3)
- Cornell University Council, 1966-1980 (Box 26, Folder 4-8)
- Cornell University Council, 1980-1982 (Box 26, Folder 9-11)
- Cornell University Council, 1982-1985 (Box 26, Folder 12-14)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1968-1973 (Box 26, Folder 15-18)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1982-1983 (Box 26, Folder 19-20)
- Civil & Environmental Engineering, 1983-1984 (Box 26, Folder 21-22)
- Cornell University Council, 1985-1988 (Box 26, Folder 23-25)
- Corning, 1961-1969 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Coming Glass Co., 1963-1979 (Box 26, Folder 27-30)
- Corning Glass Co., 1979-1983 (Box 26, Folder 31-33)
- Corporate Liaison Committee, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 34-35)
- Corson, Dale R. "The Next Ten to Twenty Years in Engineering Education at Cornell University", 1969 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Cranch, E.T. Study, 1962 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Cranch Report, 1964-1985 (Box 27, Folder 3-4)
- Crash Injury Research- Aviation & Automotive, 1952-1957 (Box 27, Folder 5-6)
- Center for Radiophysics and Space Research, 1970-1973 (Box 27, Folder 7-9)
- Center for Radiophysics and Space Research, 1961-1971 (Box 27, Folder 10-13)
- Corson, Dale R., 1961-1975 (Box 27, Folder 14-17)
- Cranch, E.T., 1964-1985 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Committee on the Undergraduate Program in Mathematics- Applied Math, 1966 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Deere and Company, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Agriculture, College of, 1967-1981 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Engineering, Dept, of, 1967-1983 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Affirmative Action, 1969-1979 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Committee on Independent Colleges and Universities, 1981-1982 (Box 27, Folder 24-26)
- Commerce Department, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Cole, Edward S. Recognition of, 1976 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- Cornell Laboratory of Environmental Applications of Remote Sensing (CLEARS) Review, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 29-30)
- Civil and Environmental Engineering (C.E.E.) Reneva!;»or» of Gee-technical Lab, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 31)
- C.E.E. Hydraulics Laboratory Expansion, 1980-1984 (Box 27, Folder 32-33)
- C.E.E., 1973-1975 (Box 27, Folder 34)
- C.E.E., 1975-1977 (Box 27, Folder 35-36)
- C.E.E., 1977-1980 (Box 27, Folder 37-38)
- C.E.E., 1980-1987 (Box 27, Folder 39-40)
- Ward, J. Carlton Jr. - (1914 Cornell Graduate, Prominent Industrialist) - Biographical Material + Correspondence, Folder 1, 1985-1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Ward, J. Carlton Jr. - (1914 Cornell Graduate, Prominent Industrialist) - Biographical Material + Correspondence, Folder 2, 1985-1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- K.K. Wang, Winner of TRW Post-Doctoral Fellowship in Manufacturing Engineering. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- College of Engineering's Committee on the Environment (CECE) (Box 28, Folder 4)
- New Faculty Lists, 1961-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- New Faculty Lists, 1974-1990 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Outstanding Teaching Award Nominations, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Teaching Award Nominations, Allmendinger - Jackson, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Teaching Award Nominations, Johnson - White, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Teaching Award Nominations, Allmendinger - Haas, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- Teaching Award Nominations, Hemami - Walker, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Teaching Award Nominations, Anton - Harriot, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- Teaching Award Nominations, Hui - Wise, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1948-1958 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1959-1964 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1968-1973 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1974-1979 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1980-1985 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Engineering College Council Minutes, 1985-1990 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Engineering College Council - Executive Session Minutes, 1958-1968 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Engineering College Council - Executive Session Minutes, 1968-1976 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Engineering College Council - Executive Session Minutes, 1976-1982 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- College of Engineering - Theory Center Executive Committee - Folder 1, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- College of Engineering - Theory Center Executive Committee - Folder 2, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- College of Engineering - Theory Center Executive Committee - Folder 3, 1991-1992 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- College of Engineering - Executive Staff Meetings - Folder 1, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- College of Engineering - Executive Staff Meetings - Folder 2, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- College of Engineering - Executive Staff Meetings - Folder 3, 1993-1994 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- College of Engineering - Executive Staff Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 28, Folder 30)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1957-1963 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1950-1957 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1940-1950 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1930-1940 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1921-1930 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1963-1967 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1967-1974 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1974-1982 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1982-1988 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- College of Engineering Faculty Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Electrical Engineering, Folder 1, June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Electrical Engineering, Folder 2, June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, Folder 1, June 1986 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, Folder 2, June 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Accreditation Board for Engineering and Technology - Volume II - Questionnaire for Review of Engineering Programs - Electrical Engineering, Folder 3, June 1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Chemical Engineering, June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - School of Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, Folder 1, June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - School of Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, Folder 2, June 1991 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Theoretical & Applied Mechanics, July 1991 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - School of Applied & Engineering Physics, July 1991 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Electrical Engineering, folder 1, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Electrical Engineering, folder 2, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Materials Science & Engineering, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Mechanical Engineering, July 1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Nuclear Science & Engineering, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Computer Science, folder 1, March 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Computer Science, folder 2, March 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Computer Science, folder 3, March 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - Computer Science, folder 4, March 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - School of Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, folder 1, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- NYS Regents Doctoral Evaluation Project - Self-Study Questionnaire - Doctoral Program Statewide Review - School of Operations Research & Industrial Engineering, folder 2, June 1991 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Glasser, Lance Director of Electronic Systems Technology, DARPA/ESTO - Visit to Cornell, October 1992 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Correspondence Regarding The NYS Doctoral Evaluation Project, 1990-1991 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Correspondence Regarding Regents Review of Engineering, 1992 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Overview and Correspondence Regarding NYS Doctoral Review, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Correspondence Regarding Doctoral Review, 1994 (Box 31, Folder 16)
- ASEE Survey, 1991-1992 (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Correspondence Regarding NYS Doctoral Review - Computer Science, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 18)